Farbstein, Leonard; Papers apap245
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- The 87th Congress, 1958-1965; 1961-1962; 3; 2 cubic ft.
  - Foreign Affairs, 1959-1965
    - Jordan, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Jordanian Visa, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Latin America, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Library of Congress Legislative Reference Service: The Middle Eastern Countries, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Libya, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Morocco, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Mutual Security (1 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Mutual Security (2 of 2), 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Mutual Security Amendment, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Near East Report, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Outer Mongolia, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Palestine Arab Delegation, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Russia, 1961-1962 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Saudi Arabia, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - South America, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Spain, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Suez Canal, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - United Arab Republic, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - United Nations, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Departments and Committees, 1960-1963
    The documents present in this sub-series deal with various departments and committees in which Farbstein was involved.
    - Department of Commerce, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Department of Defense, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Department of the Interior, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Department of the Navy, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Department of Urban Affairs, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - District of Columbia, 1961-1962 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Education and Labor Committee, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Federal Aviation Agency, 1960-1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Internal Revenue Services (Treasury Department), 1962 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - International Cooperation Administration, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Judiciary Committee, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- The 88th Congress, 1955-1965; 1963-1964; 4; 7 cubic ft.
  This seris is arranged alphabetically.
  The records found in this series consist of legislative actions, correspondence with constituents, newspaper clippings, and other subject-specific documents. Such subjects fall under the categories of: Foreign Affairs and various Departments and Committees are included in this series.
  - "A" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agency for International Development (AID), 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Animal Laboratory Control Bills, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Appalachia Project: H.R. 11065, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Appropriate Appropriations: Accelerated Public Works and Retired Workers, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arab Refugee: Proposed Legislation, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Armed Services, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "B" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Banking and Currency Committee, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield Rates, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bonneville Power Administration Finds, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Button Industry: H.R. 12253, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bureau of the Budget, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bureau of Retirement and Insurance, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - "C" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Civil Defense, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Civil Rights (1 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Civil Rights (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Congressional Procedure Reorganization, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Conservation Bill (Land and Water), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Consumer, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Cooley Bill, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Cyprus, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - "D" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Davis-Bacon Act: H.R. 6041, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Democratic National Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Department of the Air Force, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Department of the Army, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Department of Commerce, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Department of Commerce, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Department of Defense, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Department of the Interior, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Department of Justice: Mississippi Summer Project Civil Rights Incident, 1964 June 22 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Department of Justice: War Resisters League, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Department of the Navy, 1963-1964 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Department of Social Security Administration: New York Hotel Trades Council, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Department of State, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - District of Columbia Meeting, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "E" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Education and Labor Committees, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - "F" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Farm Bills, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Federal Aid to Education, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Federal Aviation Agency, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Federal Communications Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Federal Employees Pay Raise Bill (Morrison Bill): H.R. 8986, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Federal Trade Commission Regarding Cigarette Smoking, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Federal Workers: Retired, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Fire Island Seashore Bill, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Firearms: H.R. 584, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Foreign Affairs: Anti-Semitism, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Foreign Affairs: Arab Boycott, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Foreign Affairs: Arab Refugees and Other Middle Eastern Issues (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Foreign Affairs: Arab Refugees and Other Middle Eastern Issues (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Foreign Affairs: Captive Nations, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Foreign Affairs: Cuba, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Foreign Affairs Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Foreign Affairs: Foreign Aid, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Foreign Affairs: Foreign Assistance Act of 1963, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Foreign Affairs: India, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Foreign Affairs: Israel, 1962-1963 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Foreign Affairs, Israel Water Project, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Foreign Affairs: Jordan Valley Development Project, 1955; 1964 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Foreign Affairs: Jordan Valley Development Program, 1955; 1964 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Foreign Affairs: Middle East, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Foreign Affairs: Near East Report, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Foreign Affairs: Senator Fulbright Investigation of Friends of the Middle East, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Affairs: Soviet Anti-Semitism, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Affairs: Soviet Union Anti-Semitism, 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Foreign Affairs: United Arab Republic, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Foreign Aid, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Foreign Aid, Alexandra Tolstoy, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Foreign Claims Settlement Commission, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Football: Exemption from Antitrust Laws, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - "G" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - General Services Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Government Operations Committee, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - "H" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - H. Con. Res. 39 Concurrent Resolution for the Establishment of Economic Aid Coordinating Committee (Also Contains H. Con. Res. 199), 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - H. Con. Res. 40: Concurrent Resolution for Encouragement of Ownership of Farms and Homes, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - H. Con .Res. 41: Concurrent Resolution for the United Nations Charter (Also Contains H. Con. Res .314), 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - H. Con. Res. 42: Concurrent Resolution for International Economic Assistance, 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - H. Con. Res. 69: Concurrent Resolution for Manifestations of Anti-Semitism in the Soviet Union, 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - H .Con. Res. 70: Concurrent Resolution for Manifestations of Anti-Semitism in the Soviet Union (Also Contains H. Con. Res. 501), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - H. Con. Res. 267: Concurrent Resolution for the Adoption of Opposing Religious Intolerance by the United Nations, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - H. J. Res. 490: A Joint Resolution for an Invitation to the International Olympic Committee to Hold the 1968 Winter Olympic Games in the United States, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - H. J. Res. 606: Joint Resolution for National Institute of Health (1 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - H. J. Res. 606: Joint Resolution for National Institute of Health (2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - H. J. Res. 773: Joint Resolution for Seventeenth International Publishers Congress, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - H .J. Res. 840: Joint Resolution for Establishment of the John F. Kennedy Memorial, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - H. R. 1781: A Bill for the Development of Programs and Projects in the Arts, 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - H. R. 1782: A Bill for the Establishment of the United States of Academy of Foreign Affairs, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - H. R. 1783: A Bill for Amendment of the International Peace and Security Act of 1961, 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - H. R. 1787: A Bill for the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - H. R. 1789: A Bill for the Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1960-1961; 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - H. R. 1790: A Bill for the Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - H. R. 1791: A Bill for the Amendment of Title 2 of the Social Security Act (Also Contains H. R. 1284), 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - H. R. 1792: A Bill for the Amendment of Title 2 of the Security Act (Also Contains H. R. 3750), 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - H. R. 1793: A Bill for the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - H. R. 1795: A Bill for the Amendment of the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - H. R. 1911: A Bill for the Amendment of the United States Code (Also Contains Related Bills), 1957; 1959; 1961; 1964 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - H. R. 3299: A Bill for Amendment to Arms Control and Disarmament Act, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - H. R. 3300: A Bill for the Amendment for the Civil Service Retirement Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1959; 1961; 1963 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - H. R. 3504: A Bill to Provide for the Representation of Indigent Defendants in Criminal Cases in the United States District Courts (Also Contains Related Bills), 1962-1963 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - H.R. 3939, A Bill to Provide for Assistance in the Construction and Initial Operation of Community Mental Health Centers, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - H. R. 3940: A Bill to Assist States in Combating Mental Retardation Through Construction of Research Centers and Facilities, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - H. R. 4024: A Bill for Authorization to Establish a Youth Conservation Corps, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - H. R. 4025: A Bill for Amendment of the Social Security Act, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - H. R. 4166: A Bill for Amendment to the Immigration and Nationality Act (Also Contains Related Bills), 1961-1963 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - H. R. 4167: A Bill for Social Security Program, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - H. R. 4380: A Bill for Prevention of the Use of Stopwatches and Other Measuring Devices in the Postal Service, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - H. R. 4419: A Bill for Authorization of the Administrator of General Services Administration to Dispose of Ellis Island for Educational Purposes (1 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - H. R. 4419: A Bill for Authorization of the Administrator of General Services Administration to Dispose of Ellis Island for Educational Purposes (2 of 2), 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - H. R. 4635: A Bill for Amendment of the Foreign Assistance Act of 1961, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - H. R. 5736: A Bill for National Service Corps, 1962-1964 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - H. R. 6608: A Bill for Amendment of Section 102 of the Foreign Assistance Act of 1961 (Also Contains Related Bills), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - H. R. 6955: A Bill for Amendment of Federal Assistance for Education, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - H .R. 7146: A Bill for Protection of the Right to Vote in Federal Elections Free from Arbitrary Discrimination (Also Contains Related Bills), 1963; 1965 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - H. R. 7157: A Bill for the Commission of Civil Rights (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - H. R. 7157: A Bill for the Commission of Civil Rights (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - H. R. 7849: A Bill for Amendment to the Immigration and Nationality Act, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - H. R. 8075: A Bill for Medals in Commemoration, 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - H. R. 9779: A Bill for Amendment for the Peace Corps Act, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - H. R. 9536: A Bill for Dissemination Abroad, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - H. R. 10677: A Bill for Amendment of the Federal Food, Drug, Cosmetic Act, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - H. R. 11138: A Bill for the Amendment of Title 1 of the Housing Act of 1949, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - H. R. 11140: A Bill for Amendment of Title 1 of the Housing Act of 1949, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - H. R. 11143: A Bill for Amendment to the Internal Revenue Code of 1954, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - H. Res. 42: A Resolution for the Amendment of the House of Representatives to Transfer the Committee on Un-American Activities to the Committee on the Judiciary (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - H. Res. 42: A Resolution for the Amendment of the House of Representatives to Transfer the Committee on Un-American Activities to the Committee on the Judiciary (2 of 2), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - H. Res. 102: A Resolution for the Need for Rapid and Complete Atomic Disarmament (Also Contains Related Bills), 1959; 1961; 1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - H. Res. 172: A Resolution for an International Agreement for a Suspension of Nuclear Weapons Tests (Also Contains Related Bills), 1961; 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - H. Res. 223: A Resolution for the People of Ireland to Express their Will for Union by an Election (Also Contains Related Bills), 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - H. Res. 242: A Resolution for Direct Negotiation between Israel and the Arab States (Also Contains Related Bills), 1960-1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - H. Res. 333: A Resolution for Collective Defense Agreement with Israel, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - H. Res. 700: A Resolution for the Condemnation of Persecution by the Soviet Union of Persons Because of Their Religion, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Health Education: H. R. 12, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Health, Education and Welfare Department, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Highway, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Housing, 1961; 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Housing, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Housing Committee on Appropriations: Port of New York Authority, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Housing and Home Finance Agency, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Housing: North Delancey Street Area, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Housing: Thompkins Square (Transferred from 87th Congress), 1961; 1963 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Housing: Proposed Legislation, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Housing: Riverside- Amsterdam v. Planetarium, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Housing: Robert Fulton Housing, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Housing: West Side Urban Removal, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Housing: West Village (Transferred from 87th Congress), 1961; 1963 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - "I" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Immigration, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs Committees, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committees, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - "J" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Juke Box Bill: H.R 7194, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Judiciary Committee, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Juvenile Delinquency and Youth Crime President's Committee, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - "K" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Kennedy: Condolences, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - King-Anderson Bill, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Krebiozen, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - "L" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Lower Manhattan Expressway, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - "M" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Mass-Transit Bill, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Medicare, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Medicare, 1964-10-01 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Medicare (1 of 2), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Medicare (2 of 2), 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Medicare: ROBO Letter, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Mental Illness, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Migrant Workers, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Military Pay Bill: H.R. 5555, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Minimum Rate Transportation Bill: H.R. 4700, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Monroe Doctrine, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - "N" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - National Guard Civilian Employees, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Newsletter (Oct.) Replies, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Newsletter Replies, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - New York High School Incentive Program, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - New York Naval Shipyard, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Nuclear Reactor in New York City, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - "O" Last Names, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Office of Economic Opportunity, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Ornamental Design Bill, S. 776, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - "P" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Panama Canal Dispute, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Peace Corps, 1961; 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Post Office, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Postal Pay Raise: H. R. 8986, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Post Office and Civil Service Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Poverty Movement, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Proposed Legislation, 1959; 1962; 1964 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Proposed Legislation, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Public Law 480, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Public Works Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Quality Stabilization Bill, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - "R" Names, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Railway Labor Dispute, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Reapportionment, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Religious Freedom, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Rules Committee, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - "S" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - School Prayer Issue, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Small Business Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Smoking, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Social Security, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Social Security Administration, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - State Department: International Ladies' Garment Workers Union, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - State Department Publications, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sugar Quota, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - "T" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Taxes, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Taxes: Ernest Applebaum, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Test Ban Treaty, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Tips Paid Included as Wages: H. R. 781, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Three-Party Declaration, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - "U" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Un-American Activities Committee, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Un-American Activities Committee, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - United Nations, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - United Nations, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - United States Coast Guard, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - United States Department of Labor, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - United States Information Agency, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - United States Information Agency (U.S.I.A), 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - "V" Last Names, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Veterans' Administration, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Veterans Affairs Committee, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Veterans Affairs Committee: H. R. 9004, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Veterans (Part-Time), 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Viet Nam Crisis, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - "W" Last Names, 1964-1966 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Ways and Means, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Wheat Sale: Soviet Union, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - White House, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - White House Fellows (Students), 1964 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Wilderness Bill, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - "X"-Z" Last Names, 1963-1964 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- The 89th Congress, 1956-1966; 5; 7.75 cubic ft.
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  The records found in this series consist of legislative actions, correspondence with constituents, newspaper clippings, and other subject-specific documents. Such subjects fall under the categories of: Foreign Affairs and various Departments and Committees.
  - "A" Names, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agency for International Development, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Airline Strike, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Animal (1 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Animal (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Appalachia Bill, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Arms Control and Disarmament Agency, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Armed Services Committee, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Atomic Energy Commission, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - "B" Last Names, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Banking and Currency Committee, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bank Merger: S. 1698, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Brooklyn Naval Shipyard, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bureau of Security and Consular Affairs, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - "C" Last Names, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Civil Rights, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Civil Rights (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Civil Rights (2 of 2), 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Civil Rights: Selma, Alabama, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Civil Service, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Civil Service Commission, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Clippings and Other Material on the Subject of H.R. 10855, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Foreign Affairs: Resolution of Commendation and Esteem Extended to Honorable Dean Rusk, 1966 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and Release on Public Works Committee Hearing on H.R. 10855, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Cyprus, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - "D" Last Names, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Demonstration Cities, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Department of the Air Force, 1964-1965 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Department of Agriculture, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Department of the Army, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Department of Commerce, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Department of Defense, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare: Food and Drug Administration, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Department of Health, Education and Welfare: Henry Street Settlement, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Department of the Interior, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Department of the Interior: Bureau of Public Roads, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Department of Justice: Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Department of Justice: Mississippi Tragedy, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Department of Labor, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Department of the Navy, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Department of the Post Office, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 16)